[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Thank you, Piers: Good to be here.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", ",", "Piers", ":", "Good", "to", "be", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "So, an honest debate, you feel you've been muzzled?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "an", "honest", "debate", ",", "you", "feel", "you", "'ve", "been", "muzzled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, once they fire you, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "once", "they", "fire", "you", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "How would you honestly have felt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "honestly", "have", "felt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I think it was being ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "being", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "So, are you saying you were ridiculous?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "are", "you", "saying", "you", "were", "ridiculous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "No, I'm saying they would be ridiculous to try to draw such an analogy, because remember, there is a reality after 9/11.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "saying", "they", "would", "be", "ridiculous", "to", "try", "to", "draw", "such", "an", "analogy", ",", "because", "remember", ",", "there", "is", "a", "reality", "after", "9/11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "And you know what, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "know", "what", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "You still feel uncomfortable.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "still", "feel", "uncomfortable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What do you do when you get on a plane and you see the Muslim in a Muslim garb?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "when", "you", "get", "on", "a", "plane", "and", "you", "see", "the", "Muslim", "in", "a", "Muslim", "garb", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What was the honest debate you hoped to have by saying you feel uncomfortable around Muslims on planes?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "honest", "debate", "you", "hoped", "to", "have", "by", "saying", "you", "feel", "uncomfortable", "around", "Muslims", "on", "planes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "It's right there.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "right", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Isn't that what you were doing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "what", "you", "were", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "You're not putting them in a box?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "putting", "them", "in", "a", "box", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "No, and here's the thing.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "and", "here", "'s", "the", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "You have no regrets, seriously?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "no", "regrets", ",", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "I would have, that's the thing, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "thing", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "You didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "No, and I'll tell you what?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "and", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "It would have seen it as a form of racial stereotyping.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "seen", "it", "as", "a", "form", "of", "racial", "stereotyping", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "If it was, what is he doing as the standard bearer for the Tea Party now?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "was", ",", "what", "is", "he", "doing", "as", "the", "standard", "bearer", "for", "the", "Tea", "Party", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I would agree with him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "agree", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Do they have a point?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "have", "a", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, I don't know they have a point because they haven't proven it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "they", "have", "a", "point", "because", "they", "have", "n't", "proven", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["foxnews.com"]}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "-- against -- as he calls President Obama -- an African- American?", "question_tokens": ["--", "against", "--", "as", "he", "calls", "President", "Obama", "--", "an", "African-", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I wrote just such a column, just such a column for foxnews.com.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wrote", "just", "such", "a", "column", ",", "just", "such", "a", "column", "for", "foxnews.com", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Are you as proud today as you were two or three years ago?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "proud", "today", "as", "you", "were", "two", "or", "three", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "We'll talk.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "talk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Well, you know, I think there's no question we're not solving our problems, that we are not taking action, that we are stuck, we are paralyzed politically.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "we", "'re", "not", "solving", "our", "problems", ",", "that", "we", "are", "not", "taking", "action", ",", "that", "we", "are", "stuck", ",", "we", "are", "paralyzed", "politically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "I mean, as a black American, what did you feel the day that you had your first -- not you -- America had its first black president?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "as", "a", "black", "American", ",", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "the", "day", "that", "you", "had", "your", "first", "--", "not", "you", "--", "America", "had", "its", "first", "black", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", ":", "RB", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Well, I'll tell you two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Emotional for you personally?", "question_tokens": ["Emotional", "for", "you", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Has he been disappointing?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "been", "disappointing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I think the whole situation's been disappointing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "whole", "situation", "'s", "been", "disappointing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Has he personally do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "personally", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "ILLIAMS: Well, I think personally he's been trying.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLIAMS", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "personally", "he", "'s", "been", "trying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Who is the Republican who right now do you think would have the best chance of beating Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "Republican", "who", "right", "now", "do", "you", "think", "would", "have", "the", "best", "chance", "of", "beating", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "MD", "''", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Do you think he could beat him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "could", "beat", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "\"Could\" is a very strong word.", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Could", "''", "is", "a", "very", "strong", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "WILLIAMS: This is the Arthur Laffer piece?", "question_tokens": ["WILLIAMS", ":", "This", "is", "the", "Arthur", "Laffer", "piece", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Arthur Laffer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["G.E."]}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "The simplify indication of the code as a starting point for the debate is not a bad place to have, is it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "simplify", "indication", "of", "the", "code", "as", "a", "starting", "point", "for", "the", "debate", "is", "not", "a", "bad", "place", "to", "have", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "But no, and it resonates with the American public that's absolutely fed up with the idea of so many loopholes, deductions, tax credits and the like, and the idea that G.E. and others, these large corporations pay no taxes while you and I are looking at the bill and screaming bloody murder.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "no", ",", "and", "it", "resonates", "with", "the", "American", "public", "that", "'s", "absolutely", "fed", "up", "with", "the", "idea", "of", "so", "many", "loopholes", ",", "deductions", ",", "tax", "credits", "and", "the", "like", ",", "and", "the", "idea", "that", "G.E.", "and", "others", ",", "these", "large", "corporations", "pay", "no", "taxes", "while", "you", "and", "I", "are", "looking", "at", "the", "bill", "and", "screaming", "bloody", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "When you look back over this extraordinary run you've had, what do you think of your career?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "back", "over", "this", "extraordinary", "run", "you", "'ve", "had", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "your", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, I think the first thing that pops into my mind is I'm happy but I want more.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "first", "thing", "that", "pops", "into", "my", "mind", "is", "I", "'m", "happy", "but", "I", "want", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Is that the secret, to always stay hungry, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "secret", ",", "to", "always", "stay", "hungry", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "You yourself have survived ovarian cancer, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "yourself", "have", "survived", "ovarian", "cancer", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "How old were you, if you don't mind me asking?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "were", "you", ",", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "me", "asking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "It's been eight years, so I would have been 55.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "eight", "years", ",", "so", "I", "would", "have", "been", "55", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "I mean, that is the moment everybody dreads, isn't it, just right there?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "is", "the", "moment", "everybody", "dreads", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "just", "right", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I just began to shake just nonstop all afternoon.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "began", "to", "shake", "just", "nonstop", "all", "afternoon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "If you had your time again, would you go public, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "your", "time", "again", ",", "would", "you", "go", "public", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "What impact did it have on your life, the whole experience?", "question_tokens": ["What", "impact", "did", "it", "have", "on", "your", "life", ",", "the", "whole", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Well, I lost my hearing a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "lost", "my", "hearing", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Permanently?", "question_tokens": ["Permanently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Yeah, from chemo.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "from", "chemo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "You can hear me perfectly well, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "hear", "me", "perfectly", "well", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Oh yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "You wear aids on the set then, as well as microphones and stuff?", "question_tokens": ["You", "wear", "aids", "on", "the", "set", "then", ",", "as", "well", "as", "microphones", "and", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Are you completely clear of the cancer?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "completely", "clear", "of", "the", "cancer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBZ", "RBR", "CC", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "How did it change your outlook on life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "it", "change", "your", "outlook", "on", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "It sounds corny to say -- and it took me awhile because right after it, I went through a depression, which I'm hearing now is more and more common.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "sounds", "corny", "to", "say", "--", "and", "it", "took", "me", "awhile", "because", "right", "after", "it", ",", "I", "went", "through", "a", "depression", ",", "which", "I", "'m", "hearing", "now", "is", "more", "and", "more", "common", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "When you watch it back now, how do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watch", "it", "back", "now", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Like I wish I had another cosmopolitan.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "I", "wish", "I", "had", "another", "cosmopolitan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "How many did it take?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "did", "it", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "It took a couple to get in the tub.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "took", "a", "couple", "to", "get", "in", "the", "tub", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "But to see a script where it says right, at this point, Kathy, you're going to get naked and get into a hot tub, what is your first thought when you see that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "to", "see", "a", "script", "where", "it", "says", "right", ",", "at", "this", "point", ",", "Kathy", ",", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "get", "naked", "and", "get", "into", "a", "hot", "tub", ",", "what", "is", "your", "first", "thought", "when", "you", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I'm glad I did it now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "glad", "I", "did", "it", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Were you also being protective of yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "also", "being", "protective", "of", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Oh, I'm sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What did Jack make of it all?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "Jack", "make", "of", "it", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "He was very cool.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "very", "cool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Are you friendly with Jack Nicholson?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "friendly", "with", "Jack", "Nicholson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "No, I must say I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "must", "say", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Nicholson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Is he really?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "ORGAN: Yeah, he hasn't done a TV interview in about 50 years apparently.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Yeah", ",", "he", "has", "n't", "done", "a", "TV", "interview", "in", "about", "50", "years", "apparently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What's he like to be around, to work with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "he", "like", "to", "be", "around", ",", "to", "work", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "He's an enigma really.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "an", "enigma", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Because it was such a huge hit?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "was", "such", "a", "huge", "hit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "ATES: It was.", "answer_tokens": ["ATES", ":", "It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "What are you feeling in that second?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "feeling", "in", "that", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I think I closed my eyes and thought, here we go.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "closed", "my", "eyes", "and", "thought", ",", "here", "we", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Memphis", "Tennessee"]}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "What do you make of what's going on now in Washington, President Obama, the whole political shakeup at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "now", "in", "Washington", ",", "President", "Obama", ",", "the", "whole", "political", "shakeup", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Well, you know, I have to kind of go back and say that I -- I grew up in Memphis, Tennessee.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "have", "to", "kind", "of", "go", "back", "and", "say", "that", "I", "--", "I", "grew", "up", "in", "Memphis", ",", "Tennessee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Who do you mean by the rat bastards?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "mean", "by", "the", "rat", "bastards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Well, I think he has got to indict these guys from Wall Street.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "has", "got", "to", "indict", "these", "guys", "from", "Wall", "Street", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "ORGAN: Because you believe that basically that was the catalyst for all the problems that are going on now?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Because", "you", "believe", "that", "basically", "that", "was", "the", "catalyst", "for", "all", "the", "problems", "that", "are", "going", "on", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "I think it was the catalyst for many.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "the", "catalyst", "for", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Do you feel alarmed by what you see?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "alarmed", "by", "what", "you", "see", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "When you see the Tea Party candidates ant the views that they espouse, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "Tea", "Party", "candidates", "ant", "the", "views", "that", "they", "espouse", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "I don't espouse their views.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "espouse", "their", "views", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "You think Obama has it in him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "Obama", "has", "it", "in", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I think he's that in him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "that", "in", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tommy Jefferson"]}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", ",", "''", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "But don't you think, playing Devil's advocate, when you watch back \"Primary Colors,\" it has always been ruthless?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "n't", "you", "think", ",", "playing", "Devil", "'s", "advocate", ",", "when", "you", "watch", "back", "``", "Primary", "Colors", ",", "''", "it", "has", "always", "been", "ruthless", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "It's like in my hoe, we have a guy in \"Harry's Law,\" Tommy Jefferson.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "in", "my", "hoe", ",", "we", "have", "a", "guy", "in", "``", "Harry", "'s", "Law", ",", "''", "Tommy", "Jefferson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Dying to know what made you say yes?", "question_tokens": ["Dying", "to", "know", "what", "made", "you", "say", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I was married to two pricks, but one thing they can't do is lie convincingly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "married", "to", "two", "pricks", ",", "but", "one", "thing", "they", "ca", "n't", "do", "is", "lie", "convincingly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "It's a great part, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "great", "part", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111021pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "I think everyone would love to be her, huh?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "everyone", "would", "love", "to", "be", "her", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]